{"data":[{"question":"Everyone who comes to this city notice the beauty of its architecture.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"who","b":"comes","c":"notice","d":"its","answer":"3","explain":"- Notice-> notices","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Tina has an habit of upsetting people unintentionally.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"has","b":"an","c":"of","d":"unintentionally","answer":"2","explain":"-  an-> a","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"I think you should be tolerant of other people weaknesses.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"think","b":"be","c":"of","d":"people","answer":"4","explain":"-> People-> people's","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"The meeting was be rearranged shortly before it had been due to take place.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"be","b":"shortly","c":"before","d":"to","answer":"1","explain":"- Be->x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Every possible effort were made by the orphanage to find the boy's parents.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Every","b":"were","c":"to find","d":"boy's","answer":"2","explain":"- Were-> was","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"The Minister gave no precisely figures about the casualties.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The","b":"no","c":"precisely","d":"casualties","answer":"3","explain":"- Precisely-> precise","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"The new musical has been delighted theatre audiences throughout the country.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The new musical","b":"has been delighted","c":"theatre audiences","d":"throughout the country","answer":"2","explain":"- Has been delighted-> has delighted","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"They've been arguing about the motor-way extension since years.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"been","b":"about","c":"extension","d":"since","answer":"4","explain":"- Since-> for","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"I am afraid our problem are only just beginning.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"problem","b":"only","c":"just","d":"beginning","answer":"1","explain":"- Problem->problems","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Recent research shows that we use for the left and right hemispheres of our brain for different mental functions.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Recent","b":"shows","c":"for","d":"different","answer":"3","explain":"- For-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"}]}